<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation process on Sample documentation</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/</link><description>Recent content in Installation process on Sample documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Install S3 File Gateway virtual machine</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/file_gateway_vm/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/file_gateway_vm/</guid><description>In this stage, you request where to download the S3 File Gateway and install in your hypervisor.
Contact your designated company representative, and request the URL to the file gateway and the AWS region. Provide the hypervisor you have with your request to receive the correct URL. Only the following hypervisors are supported: VMware ESXi Hypervisor Microsoft Hyper-V Hypervisor Linux Kernel-based Virtual Machine Download the S3 File Gateway virtual machine (VM) image and install it in your hypervisor.</description></item><item><title>Test network connection</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/test_network_connection/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/test_network_connection/</guid><description>In this stage, you must test the network connection to your S3 File Gateway.
Log into your virtual machine. A screen similar to the following is displayed:
Enter the command to “Test Network Connectivity” and press Enter.
Select the “Public” endpoint type and press Enter.
Enter the AWS region, which you have received from your designated INVIDI representative, and press Enter.
If the test is successful, continue with the procedure. If the test is unsuccessful, then configure your firewall and router to allow traffic from the AWS service endpoints described here: Allowing AWS Storage Gateway access through firewalls and routers.</description></item><item><title>Configure and activate gateway</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/activate_gateway/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/installation_process/activate_gateway/</guid><description>In this stage, the S3 File Gateway is configured and activated. How this happens depends on whether or not the company is granted access to the virtual machine where you installed the S3 File Gateway.
The company can have access to VM If you allow the company, even temporary, access to the virtual machine where you installed the S3 File Gateway, then the company can configure and activate the S3 File Gateway.</description></item></channel></rss>