<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Live TV App Installation Guide on Sample documentation</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/</link><description>Recent content in Live TV App Installation Guide on Sample documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/prerequisites/</guid><description>Before you install the Live TV app, make sure that the following prerequisites are met:
You have the latest version of the Live TV app on your computer. If not, contact your designated company representative and request the latest version. You have the Android Debug Bridge (adb) command-line tool installed on your computer. For more information on how to install the adb command-line tool, see https://developer.android.com/tools/releases/platform-tools. Your computer and the Android TV box are located on the same network.</description></item><item><title>Security recommendations</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/security_recommendations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/security_recommendations/</guid><description>The company recommends the following security measures for the Android TV boxes installed in your environment:
Updates to the operating system should be installed on the Android TV boxes when they become available from the manufacturer. Updates to the Live TV app should be installed on the Android TV boxes when they become available from the company. The Android TV boxes should be installed in an isolated network, because the devices themselves do not support authentication, and do not have a firewall embedded.</description></item><item><title>Installation process</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/installation_process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/installation_process/</guid><description>Before you start, make sure the Android TV box is
connected to a screen, connected to your network, and connected to the network stream through its input port. Enable USB debugging and fetch IP address Although you connect to the Android TV box over your network, you must enable USB debugging on the Android TV box before you can install the Live TV app through the Android Debug Bridge (adb).</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/troubleshooting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/live_tv_app/troubleshooting/</guid><description>Before you start troubleshooting the Android TV box and the app, the Android TV box must be connected to a screen. When something happens to one of your Android TV boxes, it may be necessary to troubleshoot the device. This topic helps you troubleshoot the most common issues.
Disconnected cables USB to RF/DVB-C cable disconnected When the USB to RF/DVB-C cable is disconnected from the Android TV box (see connection 1 in the image), then the app loses the tuned channel, and an operator must re-tune the app to the correct channel.</description></item></channel></rss>