<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>File Gateway Installation Guide on Sample documentation</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/</link><description>Recent content in File Gateway Installation Guide on Sample documentation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Prerequisites</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/prerequisites/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/prerequisites/</guid><description>Before you install the S3 File Gateway, make sure that the following prerequisites are met:
Microsoft Active Directory service account with the correct permissions. For more information, see Active Directory service account permission requirements - AWS Storage Gateway One of the following hypervisors to deploy the virtual machine appliance: VMware ESXi Hypervisor
Microsoft Hyper-V Hypervisor
Linux Kernel-based Virtual Machine
For supported versions, see Supported hypervisors and host requirements)
Sufficient bandwidth between your network and AWS (at least 100 Mbps) Hardware: Four virtual processors assigned to the VM</description></item><item><title>Next steps</title><link>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/next_steps/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tinks.github.io/sample-docs-hugo/installation_guides/file_gateway/next_steps/</guid><description>In the next steps, the company sets up one or more AWS File shares as needed for your solution and according to your network file sharing protocol:
SMB, which is standard for Microsoft Windows environments NFS, which is standard for Linux environments When the AWS File shares are available, the company provides you with the necessary commands to map the AWS File share to your local network folder and asks you to send a test file to test the setup.</description></item></channel></rss>